residualforexincome.biz 2008-12-16

# Residual Forex Income - Online forex investment project

**PRIVACY STATEMENTS**   

ReidualForexIncome.com have always been committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of personal information about our current and prospective customers. We are proud of our privacy practices and want you to know how we protect this information and use it to service your account. You do not have to contact us to benefit from ReidualForexIncome's privacy protections; they apply automatically to all of our customers. 

We hope you will take a moment to review the full privacy policy of ReidualForexIncome.com. Please note that all details of this policy require that you deal with us as an individual investor (personal account holder). You are not allowed to operate through your investment conultant, lawyer or insurance company. In this case we do not guarantee privacy protection and may suspend your account/funds without any notice. 

**HOW AND WHY WE OBTAIN PERSONAL INFORMATION**   
ReidualForexIncome takes great care to protect your personal information and when we use it, we do so with respect for your privacy. We may use personal information about you to service and maintain your account; process transactions in your account; respond to inquiries from you or your representative; develop, offer, and deliver services.   
The privacy policies of ResidualForexIncome are reviewed annually. Our printed and online notices are then updated to reflect any material changes.

**HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**   
ReidualForexIncome has always considered the protection of sensitive information to be a foundation of customer trust and a sound business practice. We employ physical, electronic and procedural controls and we regularly adapt these controls to respond to changing requirements and advances in technology.  
Within ReidualForexIncome and among our service providers, we restrict access to personal information to those who require it to provide services to you.   
**Important!** We do not share your personal information with third parties like government agencies, law enforcement agencies etc. 

Privacy, security and service in our online operations are just as critical as in the rest of our business. ReidualForexIncome employs all of the safeguards described previously, along with the following Internet-specific practices. We use firewall barriers, encryption techniques and authentication procedures, among others, to maintain the security of your online session and to protect ReidualForexIncome accounts and systems from unauthorized access. We may also place cookies and similar files on your hard drive for purposes such as security, to facilitate site navigation, and to personalize your experience on our site. Our cookies do not identify you by name as an individual or by account number.

When you visit ReidualForexIncome Internet webpages, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on our Web sites. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our Web design and functionality. We may use third party service providers to help us analyze certain online activities. For example, these service providers may help us measure the performance of our online advertising campaigns or analyze visitor activity on our Web sites. We may permit these service providers to use cookies and other technologies, such as Web beacons or pixel tags, to perform these services for ReidualForexIncome. We do not share personally identifiable information about our customers with these third party service providers, and these service providers do not collect such information on our behalf.
